Luding Andrés Castañeda García Software Developer



Contact

+573193760301

in Luding Castañeda

Skills

Backend technologies

Python (Flask)

Ruby (Rails)

Js JavaScript (Express)

Go (Fiber) ⊶

Frontend technologies

5 Html, Css and JS

JavaScript (VueJS, ReactJS)

Other technologies

Docker (CI/CD)

Git (Github)

Soft Skills

Leadership

Communication

Planning

Agile methodologies (Scrum)

Profile

I'm a passionate Software Developer with experience working in the Web World, I really love work with new technologies and create creative solutions for problems using software as a tool. Usually I learn about innovation by testing Machine learning models or making mechanics in video games engines (commonly Godot), is part of my aventure spirit.

Professional Experience

Artificial Intelligence QA Developer Revelo (April 2024 - Present)

I'm working in the training of different LMMs code code generation with a variety of programming languages. As a QA developer, my responsabilices is to make a fine tunning over the models to adjust the generated code and explanation over good practices and standards

Full-Stack Developer Fusepong (Sep 2021 - April 2024)

I was making a powerful access control software with a great team as full-stack developer using PostgreSQL and Rails in the backend and, VueJS with Cordova in frontend. Additionally, we use Docker with different frameworks, usually from Python for create operative systems in micro-controllers and microservices connected with CI/CD in Kubernetes with Github Actions. All focused on create an integrated ecosystem of innovation in the Latam security.

Web Developer Freelance (Jul 2019 - Sep 2021)

Worked on a lot of independent or personal projects with MERN stack (MoogoDB, Express, ReactJS, Node), using in some cases Handlebars like template motor (for fast projects without a big frontend requirement).

Education

Electronic Engineering

<u>UNAD</u> (Universidad Nacional Abierta y a Distancia) 2021 - Present

I'm studying Electronic Engineering, I've learned C, C++ and VHDL focused in the implementation of micro-controllers and micro-processors, also I'm learning the process to design intermediate level integrated circuits for build simple electronic machines by myself.

Technical Degree in Software Development SENA (Servicio Nacional de Aprendizaje) 2019 - 2021

Basis of software development from logic to advance algorism and OOP are concepts that I learned in this institute, coding in Java and PHP and building personal web apps.